import { Question } from "../../interfaces/question";

export const questionsReactNativeSsetOne: Question[] = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'flex' property in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To control how flex items grow or shrink to fill available space",
    answerOne: "To specify the font size of a text element",
    answerTwo: "To set the background color of a component",
    answerThree: "To define the spacing between components",
    answerFour:
      "To control how flex items grow or shrink to fill available space",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'StyleSheet' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To define and manage styles in a more efficient way",
    answerOne: "To render custom fonts in a React Native app",
    answerTwo: "To handle user interactions and gestures",
    answerThree: "To manage navigation between screens in an app",
    answerFour: "To define and manage styles in a more efficient way",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'AsyncStorage' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To store and retrieve persistent data on the device",
    answerOne: "To handle asynchronous network requests in an app",
    answerTwo: "To manage the state of a React component",
    answerThree: "To display a modal dialog in a React Native app",
    answerFour: "To store and retrieve persistent data on the device",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'ActivityIndicator' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To display a loading spinner or indicator",
    answerOne: "To capture user input through a text field",
    answerTwo: "To create a swipeable card stack",
    answerThree: "To play audio and video files in an app",
    answerFour: "To display a loading spinner or indicator",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'LayoutAnimation' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To animate layout changes and transitions in React Native components",
    answerOne:
      "To fetch and manipulate data from external APIs in React Native",
    answerTwo: "To handle navigation and routing in React Native apps",
    answerThree:
      "To optimize rendering and performance of React Native components",
    answerFour:
      "To animate layout changes and transitions in React Native components",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'VirtualizedList' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To efficiently render large lists of data with minimal memory usage",
    answerOne: "To handle user authentication and authorization in an app",
    answerTwo: "To create animated transitions between screens",
    answerThree: "To manage and persist app state across sessions",
    answerFour:
      "To efficiently render large lists of data with minimal memory usage",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'SafeAreaView' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To ensure content is visible and properly aligned on devices with notches or rounded corners",
    answerOne: "To fetch data from a RESTful API in a React Native app",
    answerTwo: "To schedule background tasks and notifications",
    answerThree: "To implement internationalization and localization in an app",
    answerFour:
      "To ensure content is visible and properly aligned on devices with notches or rounded corners",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'Animated' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To create smooth and performant animations in a React Native app",
    answerOne: "To manage forms and handle form validation",
    answerTwo: "To handle push notifications and device permissions",
    answerThree: "To implement deep linking and routing in an app",
    answerFour:
      "To create smooth and performant animations in a React Native app",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'Image' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To display images in a React Native app",
    answerOne: "To handle user interactions and gestures",
    answerTwo: "To play audio and video files in an app",
    answerThree: "To create a tab-based navigation system",
    answerFour: "To display images in a React Native app",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'useWindowDimensions' hook in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To access the dimensions of the window or screen where the app is running",
    answerOne:
      "To handle asynchronous operations and side effects in React Native",
    answerTwo: "To create custom reusable components in React Native",
    answerThree: "To manage form input and validation in React Native",
    answerFour:
      "To access the dimensions of the window or screen where the app is running",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'DevTools' feature in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To enable debugging and inspection of React Native apps in development",
    answerOne: "To control the appearance and behavior of the status bar",
    answerTwo: "To handle deep linking and open external links in an app",
    answerThree:
      "To render content within the safe area boundaries of a device",
    answerFour:
      "To enable debugging and inspection of React Native apps in development",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'Modal' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To display a modal dialog or overlay on top of other content",
    answerOne: "To play audio and video files in an app",
    answerTwo: "To manage navigation between screens in an app",
    answerThree: "To handle user authentication and authorization in an app",
    answerFour: "To display a modal dialog or overlay on top of other content",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'ScrollView' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To create a scrollable container for content that exceeds the screen",
    answerOne: "To handle user interactions and gestures",
    answerTwo: "To fetch data from a RESTful API in a React Native app",
    answerThree: "To implement internationalization and localization in an app",
    answerFour:
      "To create a scrollable container for content that exceeds the screen",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'TouchableHighlight' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To provide touch feedback for user interactions with a highlight effect",
    answerOne: "To manage forms and handle form validation",
    answerTwo: "To create animated transitions between screens",
    answerThree: "To implement deep linking and routing in an app",
    answerFour:
      "To provide touch feedback for user interactions with a highlight effect",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'NavigationContainer' component in React Navigation 5?",
    goodAnswer: "To provide a container for the app's navigation hierarchy",
    answerOne: "To handle form input and validation in React Native",
    answerTwo: "To manage and control the app's global state",
    answerThree: "To render a scrollable list of items with virtualization",
    answerFour: "To provide a container for the app's navigation hierarchy",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'StatusBar' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To control the appearance of the status bar at the top of the screen",
    answerOne: "To handle user input through a text field",
    answerTwo: "To manage navigation between screens in an app",
    answerThree: "To create a swipeable card stack",
    answerFour:
      "To control the appearance of the status bar at the top of the screen",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'SectionList' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To render lists with section headers and support for data pagination",
    answerOne: "To play audio and video files in an app",
    answerTwo: "To handle user authentication and authorization in an app",
    answerThree: "To provide touch feedback for user interactions",
    answerFour:
      "To render lists with section headers and support for data pagination",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'Reanimated' library in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To create highly performant and complex animations and gestures",
    answerOne: "To handle data fetching and state management in React Native",
    answerTwo:
      "To integrate third-party libraries and APIs into a React Native app",
    answerThree:
      "To optimize memory usage and performance of React Native apps",
    answerFour:
      "To create highly performant and complex animations and gestures",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'Clipboard' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To read from and write to the device's clipboard",
    answerOne: "To fetch data from a RESTful API in a React Native app",
    answerTwo: "To implement internationalization and localization in an app",
    answerThree:
      "To ensure content is visible and properly aligned on devices with notches or rounded corners",
    answerFour: "To read from and write to the device's clipboard",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'SectionList' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To render a scrollable list with sections and headers",
    answerOne: "To handle user input through a text field",
    answerTwo: "To manage navigation between screens in an app",
    answerThree: "To create a swipeable card stack",
    answerFour: "To render a scrollable list with sections and headers",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'NetInfo' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To get information about the device's network connection status",
    answerOne: "To handle user input through a text field",
    answerTwo: "To manage navigation between screens in an app",
    answerThree: "To create a swipeable card stack",
    answerFour:
      "To get information about the device's network connection status",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'WebView' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To display web content within a React Native app",
    answerOne: "To play audio and video files in an app",
    answerTwo: "To handle user authentication and authorization in an app",
    answerThree: "To provide touch feedback for user interactions",
    answerFour: "To display web content within a React Native app",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'ActivityIndicator' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To display a loading spinner or indicator",
    answerOne: "To handle touch events on a specific element",
    answerTwo: "To manage form input and validation",
    answerThree: "To create a collapsible header in a scrollable view",
    answerFour: "To display a loading spinner or indicator",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'PixelRatio' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To access the device's pixel density and perform pixel-perfect rendering",
    answerOne: "To fetch data from a RESTful API in a React Native app",
    answerTwo: "To implement internationalization and localization in an app",
    answerThree:
      "To ensure content is visible and properly aligned on devices with notches or rounded corners",
    answerFour:
      "To access the device's pixel density and perform pixel-perfect rendering",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'Linking' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To handle deep linking and open external links in an app",
    answerOne: "To manage forms and handle form validation",
    answerTwo: "To create animated transitions between screens",
    answerThree: "To implement push notifications and device permissions",
    answerFour: "To handle deep linking and open external links in an app",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'AppState' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To track the lifecycle state of the app (e.g., background, active)",
    answerOne: "To handle user input through a text field",
    answerTwo: "To manage navigation between screens in an app",
    answerThree: "To create a swipeable card stack",
    answerFour:
      "To track the lifecycle state of the app (e.g., background, active)",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'PermissionsAndroid' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To request and check device permissions on Android",
    answerOne: "To play audio and video files in an app",
    answerTwo: "To handle user authentication and authorization in an app",
    answerThree: "To provide touch feedback for user interactions",
    answerFour: "To request and check device permissions on Android",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'DatePickerAndroid' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To display a native date picker dialog on Android",
    answerOne: "To handle touch events on a specific element",
    answerTwo: "To manage form input and validation",
    answerThree: "To create a collapsible header in a scrollable view",
    answerFour: "To display a native date picker dialog on Android",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'AppState' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To display the current state of the app to the user",
    answerOne: "To fetch data from a RESTful API in a React Native app",
    answerTwo: "To implement internationalization and localization in an app",
    answerThree:
      "To ensure content is visible and properly aligned on devices with notches or rounded corners",
    answerFour: "To display the current state of the app to the user",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'ImageEditor' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To perform cropping and editing operations on images",
    answerOne: "To manage forms and handle form validation",
    answerTwo: "To create animated transitions between screens",
    answerThree: "To implement deep linking and routing in an app",
    answerFour: "To perform cropping and editing operations on images",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 31,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'Alert' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To display alert dialogs with customizable title and message",
    answerOne: "To handle user input through a text field",
    answerTwo: "To manage navigation between screens in an app",
    answerThree: "To create a swipeable card stack",
    answerFour: "To display alert dialogs with customizable title and message",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 32,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'AsyncStorage' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To store key-value pairs asynchronously on the device",
    answerOne: "To play audio and video files in an app",
    answerTwo: "To handle user authentication and authorization in an app",
    answerThree: "To provide touch feedback for user interactions",
    answerFour: "To store key-value pairs asynchronously on the device",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 33,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'Transform' style property in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To apply 2D and 3D transformations to React Native components",
    answerOne: "To handle user input through forms in React Native",
    answerTwo: "To manage the global state of a React Native app",
    answerThree:
      "To create animated transitions between screens in React Native",
    answerFour: "To apply 2D and 3D transformations to React Native components",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 34,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'Dimensions' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To get the dimensions of the device screen",
    answerOne: "To fetch data from a RESTful API in a React Native app",
    answerTwo: "To implement internationalization and localization in an app",
    answerThree:
      "To ensure content is visible and properly aligned on devices with notches or rounded corners",
    answerFour: "To get the dimensions of the device screen",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 35,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'Platform' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To detect the platform (e.g., iOS, Android) on which the app is running",
    answerOne: "To manage forms and handle form validation",
    answerTwo: "To create animated transitions between screens",
    answerThree: "To implement deep linking and routing in an app",
    answerFour:
      "To detect the platform (e.g., iOS, Android) on which the app is running",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 36,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'InteractionManager' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To schedule tasks and animations to run after interactions have completed",
    answerOne: "To control the appearance and behavior of the status bar",
    answerTwo: "To handle deep linking and open external links in an app",
    answerThree:
      "To render content within the safe area boundaries of a device",
    answerFour:
      "To schedule tasks and animations to run after interactions have completed",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 37,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'Geolocation' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To retrieve the device's current geolocation (latitude and longitude)",
    answerOne: "To play audio and video files in an app",
    answerTwo: "To handle user authentication and authorization in an app",
    answerThree: "To provide touch feedback for user interactions",
    answerFour:
      "To retrieve the device's current geolocation (latitude and longitude)",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 38,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'Slider' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To select a value from a range by sliding a thumb",
    answerOne: "To handle touch events on a specific element",
    answerTwo: "To manage form input and validation",
    answerThree: "To create a collapsible header in a scrollable view",
    answerFour: "To select a value from a range by sliding a thumb",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 39,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'Linking' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To handle deep linking and open external links in an app",
    answerOne: "To fetch data from a RESTful API in a React Native app",
    answerTwo: "To implement internationalization and localization in an app",
    answerThree:
      "To ensure content is visible and properly aligned on devices with notches or rounded corners",
    answerFour: "To handle deep linking and open external links in an app",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 40,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'ErrorBoundary' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To catch and handle errors that occur within its child components",
    answerOne: "To manage forms and handle form validation in React Native",
    answerTwo: "To create animated transitions between screens in React Native",
    answerThree: "To implement deep linking and routing in a React Native app",
    answerFour:
      "To catch and handle errors that occur within its child components",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 41,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'Picker' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To provide a dropdown picker with selectable options",
    answerOne: "To handle user input through a text field",
    answerTwo: "To manage navigation between screens in an app",
    answerThree: "To create a swipeable card stack",
    answerFour: "To provide a dropdown picker with selectable options",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 42,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'VirtualizedList' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To render large lists efficiently by rendering only visible items",
    answerOne: "To handle touch events on specific elements in React Native",
    answerTwo: "To manage navigation and routing in React Native apps",
    answerThree: "To create swipeable card stacks in React Native",
    answerFour:
      "To render large lists efficiently by rendering only visible items",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 43,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'Permissions' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To request and check device permissions",
    answerOne: "To handle touch events on a specific element",
    answerTwo: "To manage form input and validation",
    answerThree: "To create a collapsible header in a scrollable view",
    answerFour: "To request and check device permissions",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 44,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'useImperativeHandle' hook in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To customize the instance value exposed by a child component",
    answerOne: "To handle network requests and data fetching in React Native",
    answerTwo: "To manage form input and validation in React Native",
    answerThree: "To create and manage timers and intervals in React Native",
    answerFour: "To customize the instance value exposed by a child component",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 45,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'AccessibilityInfo' API in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To retrieve information about the device's accessibility settings",
    answerOne:
      "To optimize rendering and performance of React Native components",
    answerTwo: "To handle user input through forms in React Native",
    answerThree:
      "To create animated transitions between screens in React Native",
    answerFour:
      "To retrieve information about the device's accessibility settings",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 46,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'SectionList' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To render a scrollable list with sections and headers",
    answerOne: "To handle user input through a text field",
    answerTwo: "To manage navigation between screens in an app",
    answerThree: "To create a swipeable card stack",
    answerFour: "To render a scrollable list with sections and headers",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 47,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'StatusBar' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To control the appearance of the status bar on the device",
    answerOne: "To play audio and video files in an app",
    answerTwo: "To handle user authentication and authorization in an app",
    answerThree: "To provide touch feedback for user interactions",
    answerFour: "To control the appearance of the status bar on the device",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 48,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'Modal' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To display a modal dialog or content overlay on top of other components",
    answerOne: "To handle touch events on a specific element",
    answerTwo: "To manage form input and validation",
    answerThree: "To create a collapsible header in a scrollable view",
    answerFour:
      "To display a modal dialog or content overlay on top of other components",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 49,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'useWindowScroll' hook in React Native?",
    goodAnswer:
      "To access the scroll position and events of a scrollable component",
    answerOne: "To control the appearance and behavior of the status bar",
    answerTwo: "To handle deep linking and open external links in an app",
    answerThree:
      "To render content within the safe area boundaries of a device",
    answerFour:
      "To access the scroll position and events of a scrollable component",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 50,
    question:
      "What is the purpose of the 'ActivityIndicator' component in React Native?",
    goodAnswer: "To display a loading spinner or activity indicator",
    answerOne: "To manage forms and handle form validation",
    answerTwo: "To create animated transitions between screens",
    answerThree: "To implement deep linking and routing in an app",
    answerFour: "To display a loading spinner or activity indicator",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
];
